Guide to the Oswald G. Villard Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Musgrave, Jim, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 61)
- NAE, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 62)
- NAE, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 63)
- NAE Member Biography - Villard (Box 103, Folder 64)
- NAE nominations Bowen, Edward George, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 65)
- NAE nominations Bowhill, Sid, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 66)
- NAE nominations Brown, Burton Primrose, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 67)
- NAE nominations Cannon, Robert Hamilton Jr., 1969 (Box 103, Folder 68)
- NAE nominations Eshleman, Von Russell, 1977-1981 (Box 103, Folder 69)
- NAE nominations Gordon, William E., 1974 (Box 103, Folder 70)
- NAE nominations Middleton, David, 1979-1982 (Box 103, Folder 71)
- NAE nominations Peterson, Allen M., 1972-1994 (Box 103, Folder 72)
- NAE nominations Tyler, G. Leonard, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 73)
- NAE nominations Wheelon, Albert Dewell, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 74)
- NAE nominations Williams, Everaud Mott, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 75)
- NAS biographical memoirs (Terman), 1977-1990 (Box 103, Folder 76)
- NAS, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 77)
- NAS Member Biography - Villard, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 78)
- National Research Council, 1986-1992 (Box 103, Folder 79)
- National Radioscience Society meeting, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 80)
- NSAC (National Security Agency Advisory Council) meeting, 2/7-8/1989 (Box 103, Folder 81)
- NSA, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 82)
- NSA travel, 1979-1986 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- NSA Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- NSA personal qualifications statements-Villard, 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- NSPC (National Security Planning Committee) memos, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Nelson, A. Bert, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- NCDX (Northern California DX Foundation), 1974-1990 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- NCDX, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- NNA – AERAD Active Enhancement of Receiving Antenna Directivity Patents, 1986-1988 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- O'Brian, Brian, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- O'Hagan, Malcolm E, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Villard chronological file, 1992-1995 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Villard chronological file, 1-3/1994 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- Hagn, George, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Hagn, George, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Villard chronological file, 1996-1998 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Camtronics, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Villard chronological file, 10/1993-12/1993 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Villard chronological file, 7/1993-9/1995 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Villard chronological file, 4/1993-6/1993 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Villard chronological file, 1/1993-3/1993 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- Hagn, George, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Villard chronological file, 10/1992-12/1992 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- Villard chronological file, 7/1992-9/1992 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- Villard chronological file, 1-3/1992 (Box 104, Folder 24)
- Villard chronological file, 4-6/1992 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- Villard chronological file, 10/1991-12/1991 (Box 104, Folder 26)
- Villard chronological file, 7/1991-9/1991 (Box 104, Folder 27)
- Villard chronological file, 4-6/1991 (Box 104, Folder 28)
- Villard chronological file, 1-3/1991 (Box 104, Folder 29)
- Villard Miscellaneous papers, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous papers, reports, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- DFing skywaves, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Science Museum London, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- IEE paper meeting, 7/4-7/1994 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Villard QST article "Foxhunting", 1994 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- White paper info, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Villard Awards, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Radio Netherlands article "Antenna" (Box 105, Folder 8)
- San Francisco Chronicle article "RF China", 1992 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- WRTH article, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Villard biography, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Hagn & Cheryl, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous articles and reports, 1991-1993 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- SKA index, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- CLA (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Environmental OTH, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous papers and articles, 1933 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- IEEE talk & paper, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- WRTH article, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- SRI, Stanford University, Villard reports, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous publications, 1962-1987 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Small electronics and pamphlets (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous reprints, 1957-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Sweeney, L. E. (IEEE), 1971 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Villard TR 125 markup (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Steele, Barnum TR 127 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Steele, J. G. TR 121 markup, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Steele, J. G. TR 128 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Poternra, T. A. TR 110 markup, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Roben, L. A. TR 119 markup, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Marshall & Fenwick manual, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Murphy, Fenwick, Barry TR 120 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Kawachika, Lomasney, Villard TR 124 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Lynch, Fenwick, Villard Radio Science article, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Kawachika, Villard Radio Science, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Fenwick TR 122 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Epstein & Frank TR 105 markup, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Barry, Griffiths, Taenzer TR, 107 markup (Box 107, Folder 16)
  1965
- Fenwick, Barry TR 103 markup, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Fenwick, R. B. (cancelled), 1966 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Fenwick, Barry TR 132 markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Barry, Boston status report, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- Boston, Barry article markup, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Bubenik, Fraser-Smith, Sweeney, Villard Journal of Geophysical Research article, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Villard proposal, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Photographs, mostly SU antenna, radio telescope, 1960s (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Ionospheric Radar System summary, blueprints, photographs, transparencies, etc., 1969 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- Stanford University Electronics Laboratories photographs, memos, 1960s (Box 107, Folder 26)
- LDE Alpha data sheets, 1957-1970 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- LDE VI prints, 1970-1972 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- LDE W9FUR Lindstrom, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 29)
- LDE W0TUT Prewitt, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- LDE F82F Early, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 31)
- LDE 4X4NJ Kline, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 32)
- LDE Peel, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- LDE WB6WUW Pulverman, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 34)
- LDE W9TO Ricks, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 35)
- LDE WTAXT Ritchie, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- LDE WN0YFA Rost, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 37)
- LDE W9LEX Sharp, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 38)
- LDE WB9CDF Silvey, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 39)
- LDE K4UDP Treftz, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 40)
- LDE WA0KMD Von Dielingen, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 41)
- LDE Sonograms (Box 107, Folder 42)
- LDE flipbooks, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 43)
- LDE file general (Box 107, Folder 44)
- Cosmos Club nominations, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous reports, articles (Box 107, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous reports, magazines, books, other publications, 1969-1990 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Ortenbutger, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Orr, William, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- ONR, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Olson, Henry, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- O'Kane, Enda (Radio Eireann), 1991 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- OPDA draft, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- OTHB memos, 1987-1990 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- OTH Radar, 1968-1988 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Ottoboni, Ed (Box 109, Folder 9)
- OTH Radar Villard interview, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Pell, Gene (RFE/RL), 1987-1990 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Peters, Ben (Radio Netherlands), 1989 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Phillips, Ben, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Phase Jumps memo, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Pierce, Roger, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Piezoelectricity-Kynar Film (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Pole Cats, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Power Zvi, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Posa, Leonard, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Price, Alfred, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Murphy, Leo Proposal, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- WOH5V7 proposal, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Prospecting Letters, Universities, 1989-1990 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Villard reprints, 1946-1988 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- QST correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- QST article material, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 26)
- QST article material, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 27)
- Villard notes, 1994-1995 (Box 109, Folder 28)
- QST article CTL-II, 1988-1990 (Box 109, Folder 29)
- Quake, Cal, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 30)
- Questionaire Form, Test Results, Directional Antennas, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 31)
- Radio Canada International, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 32)
- Radio Engineering Advisory Committee (Box 109, Folder 33)
- Radio Liberty Research Bulletin (Box 109, Folder 34)
- Radio Netherlands, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 35)
- Radio Society of Great Britain, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 36)
- Radio Sweden, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 37)
- Rambo, William, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 38)
- Reed, Sidney, 1989-1990 (Box 109, Folder 39)
- Reich, Eugene, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 40)
- Reprints Antenna Research, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 41)
- Commonwealth article, Iacocca, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 42)
- IEEE article, The Institute, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 43)
- Manning "Theory of Radio Detection" article, 1947 (Box 109, Folder 44)
- Bethe "Theory of Difraction" article, 1944 (Box 109, Folder 45)
- Physics World article, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 46)
- Radio Science Frankel & Peterson article, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 47)
- Science article, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 48)
- Requests for Villard Reprints (Box 109, Folder 49)
- Responses to Villard Questionnaire, 1989-1990 (Box 109, Folder 50)
- Review of International Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 51)
- Reynolds, Don, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 52)
- Rich, Richard, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 53)
- Richardson, John, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 54)
- RML (Remote Measurements Laboratory) brochure, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 55)
- Rogers, Emery H., 1988 (Box 109, Folder 56)
- Russian Research in the Field of Hybrid Technology, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 57)
- Scavedra, Raul, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 58)
- Sangean catalogs (Box 109, Folder 59)
- Sarnoff Labs, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 60)
- Schimmel, Donald, 1989-1990 (Box 109, Folder 61)
- Schroeder, Norbert (Radio Marti), 1988 (Box 109, Folder 62)
- Reprints, memos, 1965-1991 (Box 109, Folder 63)
- Scott, Gene (Box 109, Folder 64)
- Internal Visitor's Clearances, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 65)
- Sennitt, Andrew, 1988-1990 (Box 109, Folder 66)
- San Francisco ARC talk, 7/20/1990 (Box 109, Folder 67)
- Short, George (BBC), 1987-1990 (Box 109, Folder 68)
- Scientific Review Panel memos, articles, 1965-1991 (Box 109, Folder 69)
- Simpson, Dick (QST), 1979 (Box 109, Folder 70)
- Silberstein, Richard, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 71)
- Siddiqi, Moazzau (VOA), 1990 (Box 109, Folder 72)
- Si, Stella, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 73)
- Shostak, Arnold (Box 109, Folder 74)
- Villard address book & Rolodex cards (Box 109, Folder 75)
- Terman, F. E. biography typescript and related correspondence, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Villard Security Information, 1982-1991 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Villard Incoming Visit Requests, 1984-1991 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Villard Purchase Requests, 1984-1991 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Villard Travel Expense Reports, 1984-1993 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Villard Travel Information, 1984-1995 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- AFSB, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- AFSB Committee on Space Technology meeting, 3/18/1993 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- NAS Space Technology Committee meeting, 4/13/1992 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Space Technology Committee meeting, 6/9-10/1992 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Space Technology Committee meeting, 4/14-15/1992 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- AFSB Committee on Assessment of Space Technology meeting, 2/11-12/1992 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Space Technology Committee meeting, 6/9-10/1992 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- AFSB Committee on Space Technology travel, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Villard SU/SRI stationery, ham response cards (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Villard rental, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Dynamic Information Corp., 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Invention Disclosures, 1977-1992 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Publication Request, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Publication Loans, 1967-1979 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- Academy of Applied Science, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Villard paper abstracts, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 22)
- Acoustical walls, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 23)
- Acoustics, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- Active Noise Control Technology, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 25)
- Adler, Richard, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- Advanced Electronics Applications, Inc. - Isoloop, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 27)
- AFSB, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 28)
- AFSB FORECAST II project, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 29)
- AFSB correspondence, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 30)
- Alexander, W. Charles, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- Channel Clearer Operating Manual (Palomar Engineers) (Box 110, Folder 32)
- Palomar visit, 5/8/1987 (Box 110, Folder 33)
- Palomar, Jack Althouse correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 110, Folder 34)
- Palomar license agreement, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 35)
- American Academy of Arts & Sciences, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 36)
- Amador, Sergio Valencio (Box 110, Folder 37)
- Alvarez, Luis, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 38)
- American Association of Engineering Societies, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 39)
- ANARC (Association of North American Radio Clubs) newsletter & correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 110, Folder 40)
- ANARC meeting, 7/14-17/1989 (Box 110, Folder 41)
- ANARC transparencies (Box 110, Folder 42)
- ANARC article material, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 43)
- ANARC meeting, 9/1990 (Box 110, Folder 44)
- ANARC, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 45)
- ANARC newsletters, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 46)
- Antennas for Satellites & Meteor Burst Communication, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 47)
- SU Antenna Seminar, 4/1990 (Box 110, Folder 48)
- Application of Numerical Techniques to Predict Directional Signal…, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 49)
- APS-MIT Lincoln Labs (J.J. Mayhan), 1986 (Box 110, Folder 50)
- Arata, Hiroo, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 51)
- Armstrong, William C., 1989 (Box 110, Folder 52)
- Articles of interest, VOA antennas, 1986-1989 (Box 110, Folder 53)
- Asian manufacturers/Villard initiatives, 1988-1989 (Box 110, Folder 54)
- Athey, Skipwith, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 55)
- Atkinson, DE, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 56)
- Bahr, Al (Box 110, Folder 57)
- Ballard, John (TCI, inc.), 1990 (Box 110, Folder 58)
- Barnes, J. H., 1990 (Box 110, Folder 59)
- Barton, William F., 1985 (Box 110, Folder 60)
- Batroukha, Dean, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 61)
- Battelle Institute, 1964-1972 (Box 110, Folder 62)
- BBC Monitoring service, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 63)
- Bears, Dr. Yardley correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 110, Folder 64)
- Beijing Symposium, 5/25-27/1992 (Box 110, Folder 65)
- Belrose, John S., 1988 (Box 110, Folder 66)
- Bernardi, Arman, 1988-1991 (Box 110, Folder 67)
- Bernhardt, Paul, 1979 (Box 110, Folder 68)
- BIP (Business Intelligence Program) memo & report, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 69)
- BIP file, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 70)
- Booker, Henry, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 71)
- Box Loop article, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Bracewell, Ron, 1964-1990 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Bracewell, Ron sealed papers, SRI (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Brennan, Helga I. (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Brown, Orrin H., 1988 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Bubenik, David M. (Box 111, Folder 6)
- CCT (California Advisory Committee on Competitive Technology) expense claims, 1989-1990 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- CCT meeting, 2/19/1991 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- CCT meeting, 5/29-30/1990 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- CCT meeting, 5/4/1990 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- CCT meeting, 2/21/-23/1990 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- CCT, 1989-1991 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- CCT Project Review Panel presentation, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- CCT meeting, 10/24/1995 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- CCT, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- CCT disclosure statements, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- CCT meeting, 9/20/1989 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- CCT correspondence, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- CSI (Conformal Surface Impedance) research notebooks and related files, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- CSI Research notebooks and related files, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 20)
- CSI Research notebooks and related files, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- CSI Patent: Conformal Surface Impedance, 1977-1979 (Box 111, Folder 22)
- CSI Patent (Box 111, Folder 23)
- CSI notes, memos, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 24)
- CSI Garbage diagrams and transparencies (Box 111, Folder 25)
- CSI, Potential of (Box 111, Folder 26)
- Completed experiments, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- Villard experiment file - to do, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 28)
- Experiment abstracts and notes, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 29)
- REST project bibliography, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 30)
- CSI meeting notes, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 31)
- Acoustic meeting notes, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 32)
- CSI, introduction to1983 (Box 111, Folder 33)
- Bahr memos, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 34)
- Foy reports, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 35)
- Robinson memos, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 36)
- Van Geen notes, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 37)
- P3, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 38)
- Jammer Look Through, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 39)
- RSC Literature Search (Box 111, Folder 40)
- Passive REST meeting, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 41)
- 3911 Aerospace Systems Division documents, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 42)
- Stovall visit, 3/3/1983 (Box 111, Folder 43)
- Macewen visit, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 44)
- Microwave MSDA, 4/22/1982 (Box 111, Folder 45)
- Atkins briefing, 4/22/1982 (Box 111, Folder 46)
- Stovall, 12/8-9/1982 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Atkins review, 4/15/1981 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Atkins briefing, 11/18/1981 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Foster briefing, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Wintersdorff meeting, 12/18/1981 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Wilkinson meeting, 1/22/1982 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Atkins review 9/15/1981 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Atkins briefing 4/14/1981 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- NAKA, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Scaling, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Dimensions, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Visits to Sponsor, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- 8812 Sponsor, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- notes & photographs, 1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- instructions HDO, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- instructions, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Short Pulse Tests, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 17)
- Photograph proofs, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 18)
- Originals (Box 112, Folder 19)
- photographs, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 20)
- QST-LDE article #2 correspondence 2/1970 (Box 112, Folder 21)
- LDE correspondence, 1937-1960 (Box 112, Folder 22)
- LDE, 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 23)
- LDE WWV correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 24)
- LDE TIDs 9/1960 (Box 112, Folder 25)
- LDE WWVH, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 26)
- LDE Miscellaneous notes & data, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 27)
- LDE Miscellaneous notes and data, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 28)
- LDE WWV-20 diurnal variation, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 29)
- LDE Sanborn records photographs, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 30)
- LDE Villard memo, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 31)
- LDE notes & photographs (Box 112, Folder 32)
- LDE Drafts & Superceded Analyses, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 33)
- misc articles, reports, 1965-1969 (Box 112, Folder 34)
- Messenger probes article, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 35)
- RTW Pictures (Box 112, Folder 36)
- Hoax, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 37)
- LDE paper –final Williams, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 38)
- LDE general correspondence, memos, 1969-1970 (Box 112, Folder 39)
- LDE reports, general, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 40)
- Broadbent, D. E., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 41)
- Cherry, Collin, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 42)
- Hilgard, Ernest R., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 43)
- Shepard, Roger N. (Box 112, Folder 44)
- LDE call letter forms (Box 112, Folder 45)
- LDE short delays, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 46)
- Interpretations, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 47)
- Piggott, W. R., 1970 (Box 112, Folder 48)
- Unanswered, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 49)
- W1A Allen, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 50)
- YN1GLB Black, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 51)
- VE2AYU Brearly, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 52)
- Budden, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 53)
- WA5SKI Colburn, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 54)
- VE2SV Dubreuil, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 55)
- K2UBC Davidoff, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 56)
- K1TZC Drysdale, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 57)
- G3FYR Gardner, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 58)
- WA0TV2 Geiger, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 59)
- K7GCO Glanzen, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 60)
- LDE reports general, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 61)
- LDE misc, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 62)
- W5LFM Graf, 1968-1970 (Box 112, Folder 63)
- K9SGD Hall, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 64)
- G3VA Hawker, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 65)
- WN3JET Horton, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 66)
- W2NLY Kmosko, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 67)
- K1RA Morgan, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 68)
- W2AZL Scheideler, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 69)
- W0DCB Trombly, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 70)
- VK1AU Harvey, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 71)
- K71CW Olcott, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 72)
- W6WR Skeen, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 73)
- Tucker, Admiral Dundas P., 1970 (Box 112, Folder 74)
- Wederbrand, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 75)
- Wilson, R. K., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 76)
- WB2UYD Woodward, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 77)
- WN4LUR Ott, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 78)
- W8BIE Anderson, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 79)
- WA1JLV Bugnolo, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 80)
- W4DFR Campbell, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 81)
- KX6CO Cleary, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 82)
- K1MHD Davitt, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 83)
- W4LQE Dilworth, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 84)
- K4HEN Dreyer, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 85)
- WA0OCU Eggelston, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 86)
- K0DBN Fehr, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 87)
- Hacke, James Jr., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 88)
- WA6CRQ Loe, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 89)
- K3ILC Madsen, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 90)
- Mezger, G. Robert, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 91)
- WPETJP Mueller, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 92)
- Nelson, A., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 93)
- W4DH Pulley, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 94)
- Ratcliffe, J. A., 1969 (Box 112, Folder 95)
- W9NLT Scheicher, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 96)
- Sefton, Ron, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 97)
- Shostak, Arnold, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 98)
- W2UK Thomas, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 99)
- W4NAV Thomas, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 100)
- K6OL Wallace, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 101)
- LDE general, 1971-1973 (Box 112, Folder 102)
- LDE general, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 103)
- LDE Kuhlimeier, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 104)
- Russian Paper, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 105)
- Lunan, Duncan, 1971-1973 (Box 112, Folder 106)
- Lunan, Duncan (Box 112, Folder 107)
- Lawton, A. T., 1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Wier, Robert, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Quayle, Stanley, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- LDE general, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- WA0ZJN Asbell, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- LDE general, 1971-1978 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous photographs, negatives (Box 113, Folder 7)
- VOA Antenna foreign correspondence (mostly Chinese), 1992 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Chaodong, C, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Chen, Kun, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Chen, Ling, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Chuan, Yan, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Dagong, Yu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Ge, Dai Li, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- De Jiang, Gue, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- Han, Yu Jie, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Hanqing, Li, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 17)
- Jin, Shiau, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- Ke Sheng, Bi, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 19)
- Ling, D, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 20)
- Li, Qian Li, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- Liao, Tseng, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- Liu, Zhongxian, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 23)
- Ping, Liu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- Qi, Chen YU, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- Quanfu, Men, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 26)
- Qinghua, Liu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 27)
- Rong, J. A., 1991 (Box 113, Folder 28)
- Shi, Dao Kai, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 29)
- Wang, W, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 30)
- Wei, Fan, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 31)
- Wei Ning, Wang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 32)
- Woon, Apollo, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 33)
- Xiang, Jiang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 34)
- Xinrui, Zhang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 35)
- Xu, Ping, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 36)
- Yuan, Wang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 37)
- Yang, Li, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 38)
- Yijun, Wu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 39)
- Yougen, Yang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 40)
- Yu, Ma Xiang, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 41)
- Xue, Li, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 42)